export default[
   [
  {

    question:" Do you promise to maintain social distancing until the government has told to do so?",
    answers:["Yes","Not Sure","Maybe","I don't know"],
    correct:1
  },
  {

    question:"In which month of 2019 the virus was officially identified?",
    answers:["February","December","January","November"],
    correct:2
  },
  {

    question:" On which date WHO declared corona-virus a pandemic?",
    answers:["January 11,2020","February 10,2020","March 10,2020","March 11,2020"],
    correct:4
  },
  {

  question:" What is infection to death ratio of covid 19?",
    answers:["4:1","10:1","5:2","5:1"],
    correct:4
  },
  {

    question:"The term corona-virus is refered to as a single virus or a group of viruses?",
    answers:["group","single","not yet defined","none of the above"],
    correct:1
  }

],

[
  {

    question:" Do you promise to maintain social distancing until the government has told to do so?",
    answers:["Yes","Not Sure","Maybe","I don't know"],
    correct:1
  },
  {

    question:" Can thermal scanners always detect an infected person who does not have any symptom like fever?",
    answers:["Maybe","No","No, not always","Yes always"],
    correct:2
  },
  {

    question:"Corona-virus what type of virus?",
    answers:["Food-borne","Water-borne","Respiratory","Fire-borne"],
    correct:3
  },
  {

  question:"What is the minimum distance you should keep from people when you go out to buy grocery items",
    answers:["0.5 metre","1 metre","2 metre","3 metre"],
    correct:2
  },
  {

    question:"Which of the following are 100 % effective against corona-virus?",
    answers:["Pneumonia pills","Anti fungal medicines","Antibiotics","None of the above"],
    correct:4
  }

]

]